<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logbird - Gateway for logs.</title>
    <link>https://logbird.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Logbird - Gateway for logs.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 12:27:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logbird.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Filters</title>
      <link>https://logbird.io/docs/filters/creating-filters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 13:40:23 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logbird.io/docs/filters/creating-filters/</guid>
      <description>Creating a filter After you have loaded your logs into Logbird by configuring a collector you will need to create a Filter to on the log sources to see relevant events.
Logbird allows creating filters from scratch or a predefined template.
Each filter specifies a set of rules to filter the logs by and also the log sources - which are the logs you want this filter to be applied to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding an SNS channel</title>
      <link>https://logbird.io/docs/triggers/adding-an-sns-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 13:21:42 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logbird.io/docs/triggers/adding-an-sns-channel/</guid>
      <description>Creating an SNS topic Logbird allows publishing to public and private SNS topics.
Granting Logbird access to trigger private SNS topic To grant Logbird access to the SNS topic, add Logbird AWS account (423847353785) to the allowed AWS accounts.
When creating a new topic If you want to create a new SNS topic, just add the Logbird AWS account under specified AWS accounts in Access policy: When editing an existing topic When editing the SNS topic, add to the access policy Statement array, and make sure to replace the sns ARN with your correct region, account id and topic name:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Library of rules</title>
      <link>https://logbird.io/docs/rules/rule-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 13:21:42 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logbird.io/docs/rules/rule-library/</guid>
      <description> Select Service   Contribute           </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Query language</title>
      <link>https://logbird.io/docs/rules/query-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 13:21:42 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logbird.io/docs/rules/query-language/</guid>
      <description>Logbird Query Language Query language is powerful way to parse your log lines and capture data for your events.
It is possible to pipe multiple parsers together and pick only the result you need.
// foo walks into a bar {&amp;quot;foo&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;bar&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;abc&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;xyz&amp;quot;} *walks* | parse &amp;quot;bar *&amp;quot; as data | json field=data abc | fields abc // abc: xyz  Matching It is possible to match any log line using wildcards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>